codewit.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy Policy - CodeWit World News

At the same time that Codewit Networks are committed to bringing you information tailored to your individual needs, we recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of your personally identifiable information.  
In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using personally identifiable information and your reasonable expectations of privacy. This policy covers how Codewit.com treats personal information that Codewit.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Codewit.com products and services.

There are many different ways you can use our services – to search for and share information, to communicate with other people or to create new content. When you share information with us, for example by creating a Codewit Account, we can make those services even better – to show you more relevant search results and ads, to help you connect with people or to make sharing with others quicker and easier. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

**Our Privacy Policy explains:**

        What information we collect and why we collect it.  
        How we use that information.  
        The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

We’ve tried to keep it as simple as possible, when we talk about your personal information it is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Please note: this policy applies only to information collected by Codewit.com online, as specified below, and does not govern or apply to information collected or used by the Codewit.com or its affiliates through other means.  
Your privacy matters to Codewit so whether you are new to Codewit or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions contact us.

**What personally identifiable information do I provide to Codewit.com?**

Codewit.com asks you to provide various types of personally identifiable information to enhance your experience on our site.  
We collect information in two ways:

    Information you give us: For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a Codewit Account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number , year of birth, gender, Zip code, country, Job Title, Primary Responsibility, Job Industry and Company Size. The more information you provide, the better we are able to customize your experience.  
    We may also ask you for other information at other times - such as when you enter a contest or nominated for an award or participate in a promotion or when you post an online ad, when you participate in our message boards, or when you order products from us.  
    If you want to take full advantage of the sharing features we offer, we might also ask you to create a publicly visible Codewit Profile, which may include your name and photo. Whenever you provide personally identifiable information to us, we will make an effort to link to our privacy policy  
    Codewit.com uses information for the following general purposes: To customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our opt-out of cookies from vendors with whom we do not have a contractual relationship.  
    Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit a website that uses our advertising services or you view and interact with our ads and content. This information includes:  
    Device information: We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). Codewit may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Codewit Account.  
    Log information: When you use our services or view content provided by Codewit, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:  
    details of how you used our service, such as your search queries. telephony log information like your phone number, calling-party number, forwarding numbers, time and date of calls, duration of calls, SMS routing information and types of calls.  
        Internet protocol address  
        device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.  
        cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Codewit Account.  
        Location information: When you use a location-enabled Codewit service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers.  
        Unique application numbers: Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to Codewit when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates.  
        Local storage: We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.  
        Cookies and anonymous identifiers: We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a Codewit service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Codewit features that may appear on other sites.  
   **  How we use information we collect**

Codewit does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

    We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Codewit! under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Codewit.com communicate with you about offers from Codewit and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
    Kids under 13: Do not send any information about yourself to us - including information like your name, address or e-mail address. In general, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If, in limited circumstances, we do knowingly collect personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will do so only with verified parental consent prior to collection. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

**Information we share**

For legal reasons: We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Codewit if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.  
    enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.  
    detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.  
    protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Codewit, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
    We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

If Codewit is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Information security**

We work hard to protect Codewit and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

      We encrypt many of our services using SSL.  
      We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.  
      We restrict access to personal information to Codewit employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Application**

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Codewit Network. and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites (such as our advertising services), but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include Codewit services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

**Enforcement**

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**

Technology on the Internet is developing at a rapid pace, and we need to maintain our flexibility in the online arena. If we need to change our policy in the future, we will post these changes as soon as they go into effect. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Codewit account or by placing a prominent notice on our site (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

 NOTICE: Click here for practical tips from the federal government and the technology industry to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.
